爸 是你吗
Dad? Dad?
不要…不要
No! God, help me! No! No...
去吧
Go!
特种部队：母狮
第二季第一集
该死
Shit.
-你在做什么 -我看起来在做什么
- What are you doing? - Uh, what does it look like I'm doing?
-生火 -我在帮你们做早餐
- Starting a fire. - I'm making you breakfast.
-你应该让爸做的 -我就想做
- You should let Dad do that. - I felt like doing it.
果然凡事都有第一次啊
Uh, guess there's a first time for everything.
-什么东西烧焦了 -我们的早餐
-What's burning? -Our breakfast.
她应该让爸做的
She should let Dad do it.
我已经说过了
I've already made that point.
我们一定要吃吗
Do we have to eat it?
圣诞节还很久 这样我们就有筹码了
I mean, Christmas is a long way away, so we have all the leverage.
-我听到了 -我就是故意让你听到的
- I heard that. - Wasn't trying to keep it a secret.
什么东西烧焦了
What's burning?
真是够了 我只是试着想做点贴心的事
Oh, for crying out loud. I was trying to do something nice.
亲爱的 你不会是想…你在试着做早餐吗
Honey, you were not trying... You were trying to make breakfast?
-对 -不 做你该做的事就好 宝贝
-Yeah. -No, stay in your lane, baby.
我该做什么事
What is my lane?
跟我上楼 我就告诉你
You come upstairs, and I'll show you your lane.
够了 你们知道我们都听到了吧
Okay, you guys do know we can hear you, too, right?
真恶心
That is really gross.
我有个主意
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got an idea.
-松饼宫殿 -松饼宫殿 太棒了
-Waffle Palace. -Waffle Palace!
-救得漂亮 -是啊 爸 那是个好主意
-Nice save. -Yeah, Dad, that's a great idea.
-我…对 -你竟然想煮早餐…你真可爱
-I... Oh, yeah, breakfast. Tried to make us breakfast. At least that. -You're cute... honey.
-我以前也做过早餐 -不 反对 法官大人
-I've made breakfast before. -Uh, no. Objection, Your Honor.
被告的主张并没有证据
There is no evidence for the defendant's claim.
你真讨厌 我明明就做过早餐
You're such a dick. I've made breakfast before.
如果你想吃松饼 你刚刚应该点松饼的
Oh, hey. If you wanted waffles, you should have just ordered waffles.
-你不要也来抢 -别人盘里的东西最好吃了
-Okay. Not you too! -Everything tastes better off your plate.
-真的比较好吃 -不是吧 你也这样
-It does taste better. -See? You know this. -Oh, really? No.
-不要全吃光 -对不起
-Not the whole thing. -Stop.
你盘子里明明有很多美式松饼
You literally have a mountain full of pancakes.
好吧
All right.
-那一定不好吃 -新的食物链出现 谢谢
-That's gonna taste worse. Yeah. -Oh, fresh link. Thank you.
你盘子里还有很多食物 你还去拿别人的
Look how much food you still have left, and you're... oh, you're stealing.
-对啊 我没有…-是四层食物链吗
-Yeah, I know. -Was that four links?
我要留一点明天吃
I need to make, um, leftovers for tomorrow.
你的美式松饼为何有洞
Why are there holes in...
-亲爱的 -等我一下
-Honey? -One second.
是由边境两侧的犯罪集团所为
...acted out by cartels on both sides of the border,
从来没有美国国会议员被挟持为人质
though no U.S. Congress member has ever been held hostage.
美国女议员被掳 家人遭杀害
值得注意的是 赫南德兹议员一直在推动立法
It is worth noting that Congresswoman Hernandez has been pushing legislation
允许美国军队在国内部署
that would allow U.S. military forces to be deployed on U.S.
这将是本届政府 对德克萨斯 新墨西哥州
soil, which would be a major escalation in the administration's war
亚利桑那州和加利福尼亚边境
against illegal immigration along the borders
非法移民战争的重大升级
of Texas, New Mexico, Arizona and California.
德克萨斯 贝可斯
犯罪现场 请勿跨越
稍等 你需要出示警徽才能通过
Hold on. You're gonna need a badge to get through.
国务院官员不得进入犯罪现场
State Department can't enter a crime scene.
州警
该死 我拿错了 等一下
Shit. That's the wrong one. Hang on.
-这个才对 -你隶属哪个办公室
-There you go. -Where's your field office?
-圣安东尼奥 -你上司是谁
-San Antonio. -Who's your senior agent?
杰森甘乃迪
Jason Kennedy.
你打给他吧 他会跟你解释的
Give him a ring. I'm sure he'd love to talk to you.
是杰森甘乃迪探员的办公室吗
Agent Jason Kennedy's office?
你们有位叫凯尔桑福德的探员吗
Do you have an Agent Kyle Sanford?
他来范霍恩做什么 现场归艾尔帕索管
What's he doing in Van Horn? El Paso has the scene.
了解
Understood.
抱歉
Sorry.
不必道歉 你的态度正确
Ah, don't be sorry. You got the right attitude.
别相信任何人
Don't trust anybody.
联调局证据应变小组
我们距离现场有30哩远 阿伦
We're about 30 miles north of where I can be any help, Alan.
虽然我们鞭长莫及
We are 30 miles north,
但她不是 她全家都受到监控 而且她很聪明
but she ain't. Whole family's on 360. And... smart lady...
她身上有追踪器 手机和追踪器都在同个地方
she's got a tracker. Both the phone and the tracker are in the same place.
她被关在欧希纳加一栋房子内 他们会趁天黑将她送往南边
Holding her in a house in Ojinaga. Probably move her south when it gets dark.
好 派人质救援小组去救她
All right, well, send an HRT team to go get her.
我无法派人质救援小组去墨西哥 你在那边不是有线人吗
I can't send HRT into Mexico. Don't you have informants down there?
我有线人 但没有突击队
Yeah, I got informants, but I don't have a fucking strike team.
好 那我只能联络 墨西哥的联邦警察 并祈祷有好结果
Fine. I'll call Federal Police in Mexico and hope for the best.
等着看结果如何吧
See how that works out.
好吧…让我打几通电话 看看能否做点什么
All right, all right. Let me, uh, let me make a call, see what I can do.
很好
All right.
长官 我不知道 你听了这些情报会想怎么做
Sir, look, I don't know what you want to do with this info,
但我们有议员的位置了
but, uh, we got a location on the congresswoman.
她身上有追踪器
She's on a tracker.
是 长官 我哪里都不会去
Yes, sir. Not going anywhere.
我正在看
I'm watching it now.
那要看情况 是中情局还是白宫
That depends. Langley or the White House.
-是哪个 -白宫
-Which one is it? -The White House.
-小心 -今天有抗议活动吗
-Be careful. -Is there a protest today?
-犯罪集团不会单凭自己那么做 -我知道
-Cartel would never do that on their own. -I'm aware.
这是个试探
It's a probe.
别这样 你有什么想法 能跟我分享吗
Come on. Any thoughts you want to share with me?
你在过去的路上 看看墨西哥的出口产品
Take a look at Mexican exports on your drive over.
尤其是油
Particularly oil.
我会的
I'll do it.
苦日子又要来临了
It's gonna be one of those days.
我们没有太多情报 能说明这这件事 拜伦
We don't have much intel to shed light on this, Byron.
你应该找凯尔来
We should call in Kyle.
我们通过话 他在现场
We spoke. He's on the scene.
议员身上有追踪器 他们把她拘留在边境另一端
Congresswoman's wearing a tracker. They're holding her just across the border.
他们会在天黑后 把她送往更内陆的地方
They're gonna move her deeper in-country at night.
我想他们不是等天黑
I don't think they wait for night.
而是在等我们的回应
I think they're waiting to see what we're going to do.
我自己也很想知道答案
Curious about that myself.
我安排了几个秘密探员准备 在他们运送她时进行拦截
We have a few gray work guys standing by. Intercept when they move her.
-就是我们在乌克兰用的那些人 -那会引起骚动
-Same guys we used in Ukraine. -That won't be quiet.
我想他们不怕骚动 他们只是不想派海豹部队
Not sure they want quiet. They just don't want a SEAL Team.
请进
Step in, please.
长官
Sir,
我们现在知道的就是 她被拘留在边境附近
what we know now is they are holding her just across the border.
我们安排了一组人准备破门救走她
We have a unit in place to either take her at the house
或在途中拦截
or en route when they move her.
-是哪个部队 -先遣小组 我们的人
-What branch? -Forward detachment. Our guys.
应该派海豹六队去
We should send in DEVGRU.
派他们过去需要12小时
You are 12 hours from making that a reality.
我的人已经在边境了
My guys are standing by at the border now.
不行…我们不能派军队过去
No, no, we can't send uniforms over there.
你认为她能安全回来的概率有多高
What's your level of confidence that she can be returned safely?
概率很高 长官
It's high, sir.
他们在墨西哥没有对手
They do not have a tactical equal in Mexico.
-在任何地方都没有对手 -这件事会闹多大
-If they have one anywhere. -How messy is this gonna be?
场面肯定不会太好看
It's not gonna be clean.
-你希望闹得很难看吗 -我要事情上电视
-Do you want it to be messy? -I want it on television.
等我们处理完后 就会把事情推给你们
And when we are done with it, we kick this to you.
我们与墨西哥的条约 不允许我们在那个区域内行动 长官
Um, our treaty with Mexico doesn't allow us to operate in that space, ma'am.
没有任何犯罪组织 会在墨西哥政府没有参与的情况下
No criminal organization is gonna do something this reckless
做出这样鲁莽的行为
without the Mexican government being complicit.
而墨西哥政府没有受到外部极大压力
And the Mexican government would never be complicit
是不可能参与其中的
without extreme pressure from an outside force.
你觉得是俄国吗
You think Russia?
这确实符合他们的秘密行动策略
Well, it does fit their covert ops strategy,
但他们没有足够的筹码能做这种事
but they don't have the leverage to force something like this.
是中国
It's China.
我们认为很有可能 你为何会有这个想法
We think that's a likely possibility. Why do you think so?
这对他们来说是个不寻常的举动
It's an unusual move for them,
但显然让总统处于非常不利的境地
but it clearly puts the president in a very bad spot.
在墨西哥境内的美国军事行动
A U.S. military operation on Mexican soil?
这是一场政治灾难 连他自己的政党都会反对他
It's a political disaster. His own party's gonna turn on him.
而在野党会毁了他
The other side of the aisle, they will destroy him.
这起事件类似越战 让我们把注意力从东方转移开
Some form of Vietnam in this hemisphere shifts our focus from the East
而且它耗尽我们资源的速度 比乌克兰还要快
and it drains our resources even faster than Ukraine.
现在中国是墨西哥 在原油 天然气和黄金方面的…
Now, China is Mexico's number-one trade partner in crude oil
第一大贸易伙伴
and natural gases as well as gold.
因此 任何在 墨西哥土地上的军事回应
So, any military response to this on Mexican soil
都会使我们反对进军台湾的立场
renders our opposition to a move into Taiwan
在北约和联合国眼中显得虚伪
as hypocritical to both NATO and the U.N.
加上俄国现在是安理会主席 中国可以说是…
And with Russia chairing the security council... China has free rein
能够毫无顾忌地自由入侵台湾
...for a Taiwanese invasion with little to no consequences.
所以我们不能采取军事行动
Certainly not militarily,
而我们的经济关系太紧密 难以执行制裁
and our economies are too linked for sanctions.
我们也有同感
We feel the same way about it.
我们正增加中情局在墨西哥的部署
We're increasing CIA presence in Mexico,
尤其是在特别活动方面
particularly Special Activities.
我们也希望派你的团队过去
We'd like to put your team in as well.
派一 两位母狮到现场
Get a Lioness on the ground. Or two.
当然 这一切都是为了 要成功救出议员
This all, of course, depends on a successful extraction.
你多快能安排人手到位
How soon do you think you can get somebody in place?
首先 我要找到目标
At first, I would need to find a mark.
然后我还得调用情报人员或训练新人
Then I need to pull an asset or build one.
这不是…我需要时间
This isn't... I-I need time.
你需要多久时间
How much time?
-能给我三个月吗 -我能给你三周
-Can I have three months? -You can have three weeks.
11月就要选举了
There is an election in November.
我要在提名大会前搞定这件事
I want trophies on the wall by the convention.
-只许成功 -我的任务是什么
-Big trophies. -What are my trophies?
发生绑架的地区 是洛斯提格雷斯的领土
Well, the area of the abduction is the territory of Los Tigres,
-没错吧 -对
-correct? -Correct.
先从他们的领袖下手
We'll start with their leader.
找出他和墨西哥政府有关联的情报
Find us intel connecting him to the Mexican government.
母狮并不会收集情报 长官 我们的任务是打击高难度目标
A Lioness isn't designed to gather intel, ma'am. We hit hard targets.
好
All right.
在杀了那个人之后
After you kill the guy,
你能不能好心帮个忙 把他的手机…
could you be so kind as to grab his fucking phones
电脑和任何可能 有情报的东西都带走
and computers and anything else that might have some fucking intelligence?
-除了杀人 你们什么都不会吗 -交给我们 长官
-You can't do anything but kill people? -We can do it, sir.
-能给我三角洲部队吗 -不行 海豹部队也不行
-Can I have a Delta team? -No Delta, no SEALs,
你要多少秘密探员都可以
you can have as many gray men as you like.
-谢谢 -乔
-Thank you. -Joe.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
谢谢 长官
Thank you.
-上头同意了 去救她吧 -先遣小组
-You're green. Go get her. -A forward detachment?
一群没用的人 气球破掉就想找掩护
A bunch of guys so cooked they dive for cover when a balloon pops?
他们不受任何约束 乔 这正是你需要的
They fight outside the lines, Joe. That's what you'll need.
我需要的是特战分遣队
What I need is an SF ODA.
一位母狮怎么能同时消灭目标和收集重要情报
How is one Lioness supposed to eliminate the target and mine hard data?
这要求太扯了 根本无法执行
It's a ridiculous ask and it's impossible to execute.
你有快速反应部队
You have a QRF,
我们会安排一支先遣小组听你指挥
we will place a forward detachment under your command.
母狮打击目标 快速反应部队接应 柳橙特遣队收集情报…
Lioness hits the target, QRF retrieves the Lioness, TFO mines the intel.
柳橙特遣队会与墨西哥军方发生枪战
Then TFO gets into a gunfight with the Mexican military.
那交给我来操心 你的任务是找到目标
That's my problem. Your problem is a target.
你先去跟德尔里奥的小组碰面 然后找到下手目标
Meet up with the ground detachment in Del Rio and go find one.
-你的装备在车上吗 -是的
-You got your kit in the car? -Of course.
-到兰利搭机吗 -到杜勒斯
-Jet at Langley? -Dulles.
你的组员呢
Where's your team?
四散各地 毕竟他们没工作
Spread out. You know, they're off the clock.
该上工了 要他们到布利斯堡集合 我们再讨论下一步
Put them on, get them to Bliss. We'll work out of there.
凡事小心
Careful over there.
现在开始做装饰太早了吧
It's too early for decorations.
所以我们用假树 这样能享受久一点
Well, that's why we have an artificial one, so we can enjoy it longer.
我们能不能等到…我不知道 至少等到万圣节过后再装饰
Can we at least wait until, like, I don't know, Halloween is over?
大卖场都开卖了 还等什么
Walmart doesn't, so why should we?
妈说要等她回来再做装饰
Mom said not to do decorations till she got home.
这些不是装饰品 是灯
Well, these are not decorations, these are lights.
-那还是装饰品啊 -不…
-They're still decorations. -No, no, no.
灯是发光的东西
Lights are electric, which places them
代表它是改善和提升居家生活的类别
in the home improvement and enhancement category,
所以属于我的职责范围
which falls under my purview.
把灯挂上是没问题的 但如果挂的是拐杖糖
We can hang lights. Now, we start hanging candy canes,
可能就会有大麻烦了
we're gonna be in deep trouble.
一切还好吗
Hey. Everything all right?
不太好 等我一下
Not really. Hold on a second.
机尾编号NM1139
Tail number November-Mike-one-one-three-niner.
出事了 我得出差几天
Something happened. I'm gonna be a few days.
-议员的事 -你知道我不能说的
-Uh, the congresswoman? -You know I can't talk about that.
是 我知道 亲爱的
Yeah, no, I, uh, I know the drill, honey.
要等你回来装饰圣诞树吗
Would you like us to wait on the tree?
不 不用等我了
No, don't wait for me.
好 知道了
Uh, okay. Got it.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你 看来这次情况很糟
I love you, too. This must be a bad one.
替我亲一亲女儿们 好吗
Kiss the girls for me, okay?
我会的
I will.
我说真的
I mean it.
-好 我会的 -好 再见
-Yeah, I'll do it. -Okay, bye.
好 妈妈批准了 我们来装饰圣诞树吧
All right, green light. Let's decorate the tree.
查莉 你帮我拿那些装饰品 而你帮我挂灯 好吗
Charlie, you grab the little ones. You help me with the lights, okay?
德克萨斯 德尔里奥
-我们有什么弹匣 -15个弹鼓 35个30发弹匣
-What do we got for mags? -We have 15 of the drums, 35 of the .30.
-我就知道 -很开心你来了
-Of course. -Hey. Glad you made it.
我看你干脆穿一件 上面写着你是中情局的上衣
You might as well be wearing a T-shirt that says you're CIA on it.
你那个包包里有休闲服吗
You, uh, you got something festive in that bag you can throw on?
有啊 我就从装备包里 拿一件夏日洋装出来
Oh, sure, let me just look into my kit and get out a fucking sundress.
少烦我 凯尔
Fuck you, Kyle.
别担心 那里有很多选择
Don't worry, we got plenty of options for you there.
-你在开玩笑吗 -那跟你眼珠颜色很搭
-Are you fucking kidding me? -Matches your eyes.
我倒想看看穿迷你裙怎么执行任务
I'd love to see you do a snatch and grab in a fucking miniskirt.
-我可以啊 -不可能的
-I'll do it. -It's not happening.
-别激我 -我不会穿的
-Don't you dare me. -It's not happening.
这只是为了通过边境 通过后 我们再找地方换装
It's just to get us across the border. Once we're over, we'll gear up somewhere.
我帮你准备了防弹衣 你应该是M号吧
I grabbed you armor, figured you for a medium.
我有自己的装备 好久不见 寇迪
I have my own gear. It's long time, Cody.
是啊 我休息了一阵子
Yeah, it's been a minute.
你这把年纪了 好像不适合这个任务吧
Getting a little long in the tooth for this, aren't you?
-你这么想 -是啊
-You think? Yeah? -I do.
乔 你应该听过姜是老的辣吧
Well, you know what they say, Joe, beware the old soldier.
年纪大的人更有经验
He's old for a reason.
他是崔塞 是A小队的
That's Tracer, he's A Squad.
他是迪恩 D小队
That's Dean, he's D Squad.
-枪战时 我该躲在谁后面 -随你挑
-Who do I hide behind in the gunfight? -Uh, take your pick.
大家都来自特种部队 都是追捕高手
Everybody's from The Unit. We're all man hunters.
兄弟们 把东西放上车 我们该上工了
All right, boys, let's load up, let's go to work.
该死
Oh, fuck.
欢迎莅临墨西哥
来吧 你暂时假装是我女友
Here we go. Just... be my girlfriend for a minute, all right?
好 笑着看我
Just look at me, smile and laugh.
没问题
You got it.
你好吗
How you doing?
什么
What's that?
-他问什么 -我不知道…
-What's he asking? -I don't know.
我不知道 老兄 我听不懂
I don't know... I don't know. I don't know, man. I don't know what that means.
-我们听不懂 -抱歉 先生
-We don't know, buddy. -Sorry, sir.
-好 谢谢你 -谢谢
-All right. Thank you. -Thank you.
-老兄 有看到后面的急救包吗 -有 我拿给你
-You got a mag bag back there? -Yeah. Driving with one.
该死 不是这个 快放下去
Oh, fuck, just the small one. Put that shit down.
后面还有个小的 有看到吗
A small one. You got a small one back there?
凯尔 我们应该尽快靠边停 换上装备
-No. -We should... Kyle, we should pull over and tac up as soon as we can.
先出了市区再说
Let's get out of town first.
不…
No, no, no. No. No, no. No, no. No...
你们要把我带去哪里
Where are we going?
好 出现可疑车辆 有三个人
All right, bogey. I count... one, two, three.
如果他们开始吵起来 我要你介入
If these guys get squirrely, I want you to get in there.
没问题
You got it.
朋友们 我的车子出了点问题
Amigos, we're having some car trouble.
车坏了 水箱
No bueno... the, uh, radiator.
你们有工具吗 或许能帮我…
You guys got tools? Maybe you can help us.
下车 把他们的注意力引到右边
God, fuck, get in there. Go in there. Take them right. Take their focus right.
我想修车 我来度假的
Just trying to... just trying to fix it. I'm just on vacation.
宝贝 你在搞什么 快把车修好
Babe, what the fuck? Just fix the fucking car.
-宝贝 -我在请他们帮忙
-Hey, babe, just... -Baby... -I'm just asking for help here.
宝贝 那些是枪吗
Babe, are those guns?
宝贝
Baby...
是枪
Those are guns!
快上前…
Let's move. Move, move.
-弹鼓和子弹都带上了吗 -弹鼓装上了
-Then you got drums and everything? -Drums are up.
-我们的目标在移动 -在移动吗
-Hey, our target's moving. -Target's moving?
对
Yeah.
-你扮酒醉挺好笑的 -去你的 凯尔
-You play a pretty mean drunk. -Fuck you, Kyle.
你太多话了
-你没问题吗 -是的
Good?
准备好了吗
Ready?
-你要拿步枪吗 -我拿手枪
-Cody, you want your rifle? -No, I'm gonna run my pistol.
那下面有个弹匣包 帮我把它放在这里
There's a mag pouch on the bottom there, set it right.
你负责把议员带上车
You get the congresswoman in here,
让她躲在脚踏处 以防撤离时出现危险
you lay her on the floorboard in case the exfil gets hot.
没问题
-All right? -You got it.
好 大家系上安全带
All right, everybody strap in.
不要拦腰撞那辆车 撞后面就好
Don't T-bone this fucker, clip him in the rear.
只有在车内才能射击头部 不要用后瞄准器
Head shots only in the vehicle. Know your target.
寇迪 跟我说这是防弹玻璃
Cody, tell me this is bulletproof glass.
-该死 -好 大家坐稳了
-Fuck! -All right, everybody hold on.
要来了 准备好
Here we go. Brace.
-你是议员吗 -对
-Congresswoman? -Yeah.
好 你待在这里
All right, you stay there. Stay right there.
先待在这里 有人会来接你
Someone will come get you.
好 你能过来了
All right, you're clear.
-你是赫南德兹议员 -是
-Congresswoman Hernandez? -Yeah.
-你能走路吗 -我不知道
-Can you walk? -I don't know.
走吧
Let's go.
-出发了吗 -都准备好了
-We're up. -We're good.
看着我
Look at me.
我现在帮你松绑
I'm gonna cut you loose.
为了安全起见 请躲在脚踏处
For your safety, lay on the floorboard, please.
呼叫鹰巢 这是老鹰一号 我们中头奖了
Eagle's Nest, this is Eagle One. We are jackpot,
正前往主要撤离地点 请替我开道
en route to primary exfil location. Have a lane open for me.
收到 老鹰一号 左车道已保持畅通 小心行驶
Roger that, Eagle One. Left lane is held for exfil. Proceed with caution.
-注意我们四周的动静 -收到 我们正在监控
-Keep eyes on us. -Roger that. Have eyes on now.
撑着点
Hang in there.
他们对我的家人做了什么
My family. What did they do to my family?
我们到基地再谈这个吧
We'll talk about it at the base.
告诉我
Tell me.
那是我的家人啊 告诉我
It's my family, tell me!
他们都被杀了
They killed them.
老鹰一号 确认现场已封锁
Eagle One, you sure that scene was locked down?
-对 现场已封锁 -绑匪都当场击毙
-Yeah, scene is locked. -All bandits KIA?
是的
Roger that.
好 老鹰一号 他们有人在空中监视
Okay. Eagle One, they have eyes in the sky.
警方封锁往贝尼托华雷斯的路
Police are blocking off Benito Juarez.
我们得替你找另一条到入境港的路
We need to find you another way to the port of entry.
-该死 -可恶
-Fuck. -No, fuck that.
我们得离开这城市 查看你的侦察器 有发现吗
No, we gotta get out of the city. Check your ISR, dude. Do you have anything?
-叫他们找别条路线 -没有发现
-Tell 'em to find us another route. -Negative.
帮我们找一条能到达河边的路 派边防直升机跟着我们
Find us a road that meets the river, have a BP helo ride us parallel.
好 给我们点时间搜寻替代路线
All right, everyone, give us a minute to seek an alternate route.
后方注意 敌人盯上我们了
Heads up in the back. Enemy has eyes on.
六点钟方向有敌人 距离150米 接近中
Enemy vehc, six o'clock, 150 meters and closing.
-乔 左边交给你 -好
-Okay, Joe, you got left side. -Got it.
不 你负责右边 乔 左边交给我
And I'll take right side, Joe. I got nine o'clock at your right side.
-有开火许可 -当然 快射啊
-Permission to fire. -Yeah, fucking shoot him.
鹰巢 我需要指示路线 还有撤离点位置 现在就要
Eagle's Nest, I need a route and an extraction point fucking now!
九点钟方向
Nine o'clock!
请重复…
Say again. Say again.
往北三公里后右转 有一条通往河边的蜿蜒土路
Three kilos north, turn right. There's a dirt road that winds to the river.
从道路到河岸有高度落差
There's a drop-off from the road to the riverbank.
-那有多高 -从空中无法判断 约六到八尺
-How big's the drop-off? -Unclear from the air. Six or eight feet.
往北三公里后右转会有一条土路
Three klicks north, dirt road on the right,
蜿蜒通往河边 有八尺的高度落差
winds the river, drops off about eight feet.
-八尺 -对 不是我选的 就是八尺
-Eight feet? -Yeah. I didn't pick it. It's-it's eight feet.
好 后面又来敌人了
All right. In the back, fresh bags.
重装子弹
Reload.
有两台可疑车辆正在接近
I got two bogeys inbound.
是四台
Make that four!
现在后面有很多人在追我们
We have got a lot of fucking heat on our ass.
又来了两台
There's two more!
寇迪 来接应我们
Cody, get us out of here!
乔 给我步枪 好吗
Joe, pass me my rifle, would you?
-你想在哪里解决他们 -路面上
-Where you want to do this? -Look, we gotta do this on the pavement.
否则开进土路后 这些悍马车就能从侧面包抄
We get on the dirt, those Humvees are gonna move to flank us.
-我们要在这里解决他们 -为何要停下来
We're gonna intercept up here.
我得跟你换位置
We need to switch sides.
动作快
Now!
-准备好了吗 -准备好了
-All right, are we ready? -Ready.
好 三 二 一 来吧
All right, and three, two, one. Here we go.
-装弹 -撑住
-Load up! Load up! -Load up!
好了
Run!
下车…
We're off! We're up!
我们快走
Let's go!
-该死 -大家没事吧
-Fuck. -Anybody hit?
-迪恩 崔塞 -没事
-Dean, Tracer. We're up. -Good.
-扶着方向盘 -好
-Take the wheel. -Yep.
老鹰一号 往北半公里就是河边 就在正前方
Eagle One... Swap 'em out. river's a half klick to the north straight ahead of you.
请注意 三点钟方向有军用车辆接近
Be advised, military vehicles approaching from your three o'clock.
这下一定会很惊险
It's gonna be close.
我们是从八尺高的地方直接落入河中 还是从八尺高的地方
Is it eight feet and then river? Or is it eight feet
先掉在河岸上 然后才落入河中
and then riverbank and then river?
-什么 -呼叫鹰巢
-What? -Eagle's Nest.
从八尺高的地方下去后 是河还是河岸
The depression eight feet above the river itself or the riverbank?
-直接就是河 老鹰一号 -水有多深
-Directly above the river, Eagle One. -Depth?
挺深的 犯罪集团 不会让移民从这里渡河
Pretty deep. Cartel won't cross migrants here.
东边有个更好的渡河位置
There's a better place to cross to the east,
但你需要往敌方车辆的方向开
but you'll need to turn toward the approaching vehicles.
往敌车方向开比较容易渡河
Better crossing towards enemy vehcs.
不需要轻松的路 水越深越好
We don't want a better crossing. We want deep.
我们要下水了 扔掉所有会让你变重的东西
We're going in water. Dump everything that'll weigh you down. I need you on this side right now.
扔掉弹匣 随身武器 把一切都扔了
Dump mags, dump sidearms, dump everything.
呼叫鹰巢 这是老鹰二号 我们需要空中支援
Eagle's Nest, this is Eagle Two. We need some fucking air support down here!
老鹰二号 有直升机接近中
Eagle Two, a little bird is inbound.
-预计到达时间 -朕看到了 两点钟方向
-ETA?! -I got a visual, two o'clock.
所有人戴上头套
Everybody, face coverings all around.
-我帮你系安全带 -保护脸部
-I'm gonna strap you. -Cover your faces!
-凯尔 -什么事
-Kyle? -Yeah?
如果我们能活下来 我发誓 我会杀了你
If we get through this, I swear to fucking God I'm gonna kill you.
我希望你能有那个机会
I hope you get the chance.
他们紧追在后 坐稳了
In the back, hold on.
-她系上安全带了吗 -五秒 系上了
-Is she strapped in? -Five seconds. She is strapped in. I'm not strapped in.
-要来了 扶稳 -给我五秒
-Here we go. Oh, boy. -I need five seconds, Cody.
我不知道要怎么给你五秒
I don't think I can give it to you. I don't think I can slow down.
-寇迪 这里不止八尺 -朕看到了
-That's more than eight feet. -I'm aware.
-寇迪 那比八尺还高 -我知道
-Cody, it's bigger than eight feet! -I'm fucking aware.
撑住
Hang on!
-可恶 -趴下
-Shit! -Get down!
找掩护
Cover!
-该死 趴下 -别起来
-Fuck. Get down! -Stay down!
低头…
-Heads down! -Heads down.
好了 所有人马上离开车子…
All right, everybody, out of the vehicle. Get out of the fucking vehicle right now.
-卡住了 -切开它
-It's stuck! -Cut it!
拉她出去
Get out!
来吧
Come on.
-寇迪 你踩得到地吗 -必须用游的
-Cody, can you stand? -It's gonna be a swim.
过来我这里 游过来 来我这里…
Come with me. Come on. Come to me. Come to me.
来 你做到了
Come here. You're all right. We got you.
开门
Get it open!
边境巡警
凯尔 帮我把他拉出来 他死了
Kyle, help me get him out of here. He's gone.
在一连串惊人的事件中 美国执法部门成功救出
In an incredible unfolding of events, U.S. law enforcement made a daring rescue
赫南德兹议员 画面中护送她的是…
of Congresswoman Hernandez, seen escorted by what
联调局人质救援小组
we are told was FBI's HRT team.
-消息指出 联调局探员…-怎么了 发生什么事
-Sources say FBI agents made... -What was that. What happened?
没什么 我只是在看新闻
Whatever, it's just the news, um...
来吃晚餐吧 查莉 你想吃什么
Let's start supper. Charlie, what do you want?
冰淇淋
Ice cream.
冰淇淋 不行 冰淇淋是晚餐后的甜点
Ice cream? No. Ice cream sounds like an after-dinner type deal.
先想想正餐要吃什么
Let's talk about the dinner part of the deal.
我们可以跳过正餐 直接吃冰淇淋
We skip the dinner part of the deal, and skip to the ice cream part of the meal.
好了 别再讨价还价了
Okay. Lot of deals going on there.
饼干披萨
被掳议员于墨西哥边境获救
现在怎么办
What now?
什么怎么办
What now what?
你们接下来要怎么做
What do you do next?
我们现在要进攻
Now we play offense.
帮我个忙
Do me a favor.
-我会尽力 -我是民选官员
-I'll try. -I'm an elected official.
我应该保持冷静 只追求正义 别无其他
I should remain unemotional, and seek justice and nothing else.
但在这之前 我是一位妻子和母亲
But I'm gonna be a wife and mother first.
当你找到绑架我的人…
When you find the people that did this to me...
寻求正义要找另一个部门
Justice is a different agency.
我的部门不涉足法庭
My agency... doesn't do courtrooms.
很好
Good.
你不是在开玩笑
You weren't kidding.
果然姜是老的辣
Beware of the old soldier.
是啊 我们还是有点用处的
Yeah. We still have our uses.
要来一根吗
You want one?
-我不抽烟 -好吧
-I don't smoke. -Yeah.
我也是
Neither do I.
我很遗憾迪恩死了
I'm sorry about Dean.
你知道吗
You know, of all...
我跟他一起出生入死那么多次
the shit we got into...
他没有中弹过
...it weren't no bullet that got him.
也没遇过土制炸弹 直升机坠毁事件
Or IED or some fucking helo crash,
或其他倒霉事
or any of the other shit out there, nope.
这次却因为 选择坐进大型休旅车后座送命
It's just... chose to climb in the back of a Suburban.
但这就是战争 不会有合理解释
But that's war, you know? Can't make no sense of it.
没有
No.
你会参与这次的任务吗
Are you sticking around for this deal?
通常只有在任务搞砸时 他们才会派我出马
Yeah, they usually only send me in when the deal gets real fucked up.
但如果是你搞砸任务
But... if you fuck up the deal,
我会马上赶到
I'll come a-runnin'.
有你加入我会很开心
Be lucky to have you.
至少你能减少那位肯尼带来的麻烦
At least you can offset the level of fucking dipshit that comes with this Ken doll.
对老间谍芭比手下留情啊
Go easy on ol' spy Barbie, there.
王八蛋
Hey, motherfucker.
天啊
-我就让你这一拳 -你等着看吧
-That was your one free shot. -I'll take my fucking chances.
可恶
Fuck!
可恶 乔 该死
Goddamn it, Joe. Shit.
我有家人
I have a fucking family.
我们毫无计划在沙漠里自杀式乱闯 你差点害死我们
We go kamikaze through the desert with no fucking plan. You almost got us killed!
毫无计划 我们明明执行了计划 乔
No fucking plan? We just executed the fucking plan, Joe!
而且成功了
And it worked.
-她被救出了 -我们少了一个人
-She's back. -And we're a man down.
失去同伴是代价 这点我们都很清楚
Man down is the price. And we all signed up to pay it.
你上次参加枪战是什么时候
When's the last time you were in a firefight?
我不是说某个花瓶的保镖
And I'm not talking about some bimbo's bodyguard.
-去你的 -我是说真正的战争
-Fuck you! -I mean a fucking battle.
已经有一阵子了吧
It's been a while, hasn't it?
这样吧 我再让你打一拳
I'll tell you what. I'll give you another one.
你需要释放肾上腺素 朝这里打吧
You need an adrenaline dump, fucking dump it right here.
我们现在要携手合作
We're working together now.
如果你想冒险行事 你自己去吧
You want to do some fucking cowboy shit, you do it on your own.
不要把我的队员拖下水
Never fucking do it with my team.
你知道如果我是你的话 我会怎么做吗
You know what I would be doing if I were you?
你说 我很想听
I ca... I can't wait to hear this.
我会打给家人
I'd be calling that family you got.
你说得对 我确实该那么做
You're right. That's exactly what I should be doing.
这样应该够了 把它均匀摊开
-That should be enough. -It's sticky. You just, like, spread it all...
它没办法黏在锅子里 爸
It's not sticking to the pan, Dad.
他应该没放奶油
-你没事吧 -是啊
-You okay? -Yeah.
今天工作很辛苦吧
Rough day at the office, huh?
可以这么说
You can say that.
女儿们在旁边吗
Are the girls there?
-我能跟她们说话吗 -可以…
-Can I talk to them? -Yeah.
-你要找哪一个 -开扩音吧
Yeah, uh, which one?
-你可能也要帮我弄 -都散开了
-Just put me on speaker. -It's falling apart.
宝贝们 是妈妈
Girls, it's your mother.
-你好 -你好 妈
-Hi! -Hi, Mom.
妈 你还好吗
Mom, are you okay?
宝贝 我没事
Hi, baby. I'm fine.
-我很好 -你确定吗
-I'm good. -Are you sure?
我很好
I'm... I'm great,
我很好 你好吗
I'm great. How are you?
-我们在做晚餐 -是吗 你们晚餐吃什么
-We're making supper. -Oh, yeah, what's for supper?
-饼干披萨 -那是什么
-Pizookie. -A what?
妈 就是用整包饼干面团
Well, Mom, you take a whole batch of cookie dough
铺平在铸铁锅里 然后就能做出披萨大小的饼干
and you spread it out in an iron skillet. And it makes a cookie the size of a pizza.
这就是饼干披萨
A pizookie.
听起来很健康呢
That sounds... healthy.
如果配冰淇淋吃就很健康 因为冰淇淋是用牛奶做的
It is if you have ice cream with it. They make ice cream out of milk.
-她们把你教得很好 亲爱的 -是啊 我知道
-Boy, do they have you trained, baby. -Oh, yeah, I'm aware.
-真希望我也能吃一点 -可以啊
-I sure wish I could have some. -You can.
你什么时候回家
When are you coming home?
很快 宝贝 我很快就回去
Soon, baby. Soon.
我爱你们
I love you. Love you.
-我也爱你 -爱你 妈
-Love you, too. -Love you, Mom.
再见
Bye-bye.
字幕翻译：罗惠婷